<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Gujarat Santana; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard lessons from 4 years in various software companies</title>
      <link>https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/four-year-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/four-year-experience/</guid>
      <description>I have been in various type of companies from early start-up, mid-start-up, and big company. And doing some freelance jobs. Doing some front-end and back-end jobs. It is very exciting journey and yet chalengging and also painful.
How I felt to be Software Developer in the industry My honest opinion when become a Software Developer is I don&amp;rsquo;t have a life like my friends do who are pursuing different career like Lawyer, Accountant, Doctor, Teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup my own blog using Hugo, sass, and Gulp</title>
      <link>https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/setup-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gujarats.github.io/blog/post/setup-blog/</guid>
      <description>Installation There are several steps to setup this blog so that it is up and running in your local using hugo, sass, and gulp.
Install Hugo I&amp;rsquo;m using Ubuntu 16.04 and the easiest way to install it is to download the package from : https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo/releases you can choose .deb and install it
Install gulp You need to have npm installed so that you can just run this command
npm install -g gulp  Install sass In ubuntu you need to install ruby first so here is the steps :</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>